id	page	image_slot	file_name	placement	image_purpose_and_generation_prompt
1	home	hero-main	hero-main.webp	Homepage Hero	"Main hero visual showing a premium modern e-commerce/digital technology workspace, laptop and mobile UI mockups, sophisticated dark premium environment, subtle purple-blue ambient glow, realistic high-end commercial photography mixed with UI visualization, clean composition with generous negative space for text, no readable brand names, no watermark, no people, 16:9"
2	home	hero-floating-ui	hero-floating-ui.webp	Homepage Hero	"Premium floating digital interface elements for a company website hero: laptop dashboard, smartphone commerce screen, analytics cards, code snippets and subtle 3D UI panels, dark graphite background, elegant purple and electric-blue accent lighting, realistic product visualization, clean minimal composition, no logos, no readable text, no watermark, 16:9"
3	home	brand-marquee	brand-marquee-bg.webp	Branding Marquee	"Abstract premium technology texture for a horizontal brand/trust marquee, very subtle dark graphite surface, fine grid lines, soft light reflections, minimal futuristic corporate aesthetic, designed to sit behind logos or text, no objects, no logos, no text, no watermark, 16:9"
4	home	about-intro	about-intro.webp	About / Introduction	"Premium corporate technology team environment showing a modern digital workspace with multiple screens, clean architecture, subtle human presence only as distant silhouettes, sophisticated lighting, realistic photography, high-end agency website aesthetic, no recognizable faces, no text, no logos, no watermark, 4:3"
5	home	services-overview	services-overview.webp	Services Section	"Abstract premium digital services visual combining web development, e-commerce, mobile apps, analytics and cloud technology represented through elegant floating interface panels and geometric forms, dark luxury technology aesthetic, subtle purple-blue illumination, no logos, no readable text, no watermark, 4:3"
6	home	process-visual	process-visual.webp	How We Work / Process	"Premium visual representing a digital product development process from strategy to design to development to launch, connected stages with elegant glass-like UI cards and thin lines, dark graphite background, sophisticated purple-blue lighting, clean corporate style, no readable text, no logos, no watermark, 16:9"
7	home	why-us	why-us.webp	Why Choose Us	"High-end corporate technology image representing reliability, performance and scalable digital systems: modern server architecture, analytics interface and abstract shield/security element, premium dark environment, realistic and polished, no logos, no readable text, no watermark, 4:3"
8	home	cta-background	cta-background.webp	Final CTA	"Premium abstract digital background for a company call-to-action section, flowing light trails and subtle geometric technology patterns on a deep graphite background, sophisticated purple-blue highlights, lots of negative space, elegant and minimal, no text, no logos, no watermark, 16:9"
9	about	about-hero	about-hero.webp	About Page Hero	"Premium corporate technology company environment, modern creative development studio, architectural interior, large digital displays, sophisticated dark and neutral palette, cinematic commercial photography, spacious composition, no recognizable people, no logos, no readable text, no watermark, 16:9"
10	about	company-story	company-story.webp	Company Story	"Authentic premium digital agency team workspace showing collaboration around modern computers and digital interfaces, diverse professionals viewed naturally from side/back, warm professional lighting, realistic corporate photography, no recognizable faces, no logos, no readable text, no watermark, 4:3"
11	about	values	values.webp	Mission / Values	"Elegant abstract visual representing innovation, trust, growth and collaboration using connected geometric forms, subtle human-centered symbolism, premium corporate technology aesthetic, dark graphite and restrained purple-blue accents, no text, no logos, no watermark, 1:1"
12	about	team	team-placeholder.webp	Team Section	"Premium professional technology team portrait in a modern studio office, diverse developers and designers, natural confident expressions, sophisticated business-casual styling, cinematic soft lighting, realistic photography, clean background, no text, no logos, no watermark, 4:3"
13	services	services-hero	services-hero.webp	Services Page Hero	"Premium digital solutions visual with layered browser windows, e-commerce storefront, mobile application and analytics dashboard floating in a sophisticated dark environment, elegant purple-blue illumination, realistic 3D product visualization, no logos, no readable text, no watermark, 16:9"
14	services	web-development	web-development.webp	Web Development Service	"High-end responsive website interface displayed across desktop, tablet and smartphone devices, modern premium UI, clean typography blocks without readable text, sophisticated dark studio setup, realistic product render, no logos, no watermark, 4:3"
15	services	ecommerce-development	ecommerce-development.webp	E-commerce Service	"Premium e-commerce storefront interface displayed on desktop and smartphone, product cards, shopping cart, analytics and checkout concepts, elegant modern UI, sophisticated dark background, subtle purple-blue lighting, no brand logos, no readable text, no watermark, 4:3"
16	services	mobile-app-development	mobile-app-development.webp	Mobile App Service	"Premium smartphone application mockups showing polished business and commerce interfaces, multiple floating screens, realistic device materials, sophisticated dark studio environment, subtle purple-blue ambient light, no readable text, no logos, no watermark, 4:3"
17	services	backend-api	backend-api.webp	Backend / API Service	"Abstract enterprise backend architecture visualization: API nodes, secure data flows, cloud infrastructure and database connections, elegant 3D network structure, dark graphite background, subtle purple-blue lighting, premium technology aesthetic, no text, no logos, no watermark, 16:9"
18	services	performance-optimization	performance-optimization.webp	Performance / Speed Service	"Premium visual representing website performance optimization: fast-loading web interface, speed gauge, performance analytics and clean technical dashboard, elegant modern UI, dark graphite background, subtle purple-blue accents, no readable text, no logos, no watermark, 4:3"
19	services	service-process	service-process.webp	Service Process	"Elegant visual timeline showing discovery, design, development, testing and launch as connected premium UI stages, dark sophisticated corporate environment, subtle depth and lighting, clean minimal composition, no readable text, no logos, no watermark, 16:9"
20	portfolio	portfolio-hero	portfolio-hero.webp	Portfolio Page Hero	"Premium showcase of multiple modern digital products displayed as floating browser and smartphone mockups, sophisticated dark studio environment, elegant reflections and subtle purple-blue ambient lighting, no readable text, no logos, no watermark, 16:9"
21	portfolio	case-study-01	case-study-01.webp	Portfolio Case Study	"Premium e-commerce website case study mockup on desktop and smartphone, polished storefront, product imagery, analytics and conversion-focused UI, realistic high-end presentation, no real company branding, no readable text, no watermark, 4:3"
22	portfolio	case-study-02	case-study-02.webp	Portfolio Case Study	"Premium corporate website case study shown across laptop and mobile devices, sophisticated typography and visual layout, realistic studio product render, dark neutral background, no logos, no readable text, no watermark, 4:3"
23	portfolio	case-study-03	case-study-03.webp	Portfolio Case Study	"Premium SaaS dashboard case study displayed on large monitor and tablet, analytics charts, cards and data visualization, realistic product mockup, sophisticated dark environment, no readable text, no logos, no watermark, 4:3"
24	portfolio	portfolio-bottom	portfolio-bottom.webp	Portfolio CTA	"Abstract premium digital creative background for portfolio CTA, flowing geometric forms and subtle interface fragments, deep graphite surface with restrained purple-blue glow, clean negative space, no text, no logos, no watermark, 16:9"
25	industries	industries-hero	industries-hero.webp	Industries Page Hero	"Premium collage of industries powered by digital technology: e-commerce, retail, healthcare, education, finance and logistics represented through elegant modern visual symbols and realistic environments, cohesive corporate aesthetic, no logos, no readable text, no watermark, 16:9"
26	industries	retail-ecommerce	retail-ecommerce.webp	Retail / E-commerce Industry	"Modern premium retail and e-commerce environment with digital storefront, shopping interface and product analytics displayed on devices, realistic commercial photography mixed with subtle UI, no brand logos, no readable text, no watermark, 4:3"
27	industries	business-solutions	business-solutions.webp	Business / Enterprise Industry	"Modern enterprise office environment with professionals interacting with digital dashboards and workflow systems, sophisticated corporate photography, natural lighting, premium clean aesthetic, no recognizable faces, no logos, no readable text, no watermark, 4:3"
28	blog	blog-hero	blog-hero.webp	Blog Page Hero	"Editorial-style premium technology workspace with laptop, notebook, abstract UI graphics and soft cinematic lighting, sophisticated dark neutral palette, modern business publication aesthetic, no readable text, no logos, no watermark, 16:9"
29	blog	blog-card-01	blog-card-01.webp	Blog Card	"Premium editorial technology image about modern web development, laptop showing abstract code and polished interface, sophisticated lighting, realistic photography, no readable code, no logos, no watermark, 16:9"
30	blog	blog-card-02	blog-card-02.webp	Blog Card	"Premium editorial image about e-commerce growth and digital business, modern storefront analytics displayed on devices, sophisticated commercial photography, no logos, no readable text, no watermark, 16:9"
31	blog	blog-card-03	blog-card-03.webp	Blog Card	"Premium editorial image about website performance and optimization, speed analytics interface and modern device mockup, dark sophisticated technology aesthetic, no logos, no readable text, no watermark, 16:9"
32	contact	contact-hero	contact-hero.webp	Contact Page Hero	"Premium modern business meeting environment with laptop, digital interface and subtle architectural background, welcoming but sophisticated corporate atmosphere, realistic photography, no recognizable faces, no logos, no readable text, no watermark, 16:9"
33	contact	contact-office	contact-office.webp	Contact / Office	"Premium modern technology office exterior/interior, clean architecture, subtle evening lighting, trustworthy corporate visual, realistic commercial photography, no signs, no logos, no readable text, no watermark, 4:3"
34	contact	contact-map	contact-map.webp	Contact Location	"Elegant abstract map/location visual for a technology company contact section, dark graphite map surface, subtle route lines and location marker, premium minimal design, no real addresses, no readable text, no logos, no watermark, 16:9"
35	global	footer-texture	footer-texture.webp	Global Footer	"Subtle premium dark technology texture for website footer, fine grid, soft light gradients, barely visible geometric pattern, minimal corporate aesthetic, designed not to compete with footer content, no text, no logos, no watermark, 16:9"
